("Redemption Song" by
Bob Marley & The Wailers)
♪ Old pirates, yes, they rob I ♪
♪ Sold I to the merchant ships ♪
♪ Minutes after they took I ♪
♪ From the bottomless pit ♪
♪ But my hand was made strong ♪
♪ By the hand of the Almighty ♪
♪ We forward in
this generation ♪
♪ Triumphantly ♪
♪ Won't you help to sing ♪
♪ These songs of freedom? ♪
♪ 'Cause all I ever have ♪
♪ Redemption songs ♪
♪ Emancipate yourselves
from mental slavery ♪
♪ None but ourselves
can free our minds ♪
♪ Have no fear for
atomic energy ♪
♪ 'Cause none of them
can stop the time ♪
♪ How long shall they
kill our prophets ♪
♪ While we stand
aside and look? ♪
♪ Oooh! ♪
♪ Some say it's
just a part of it ♪
♪ We've got to
fulfill the book ♪
♪ Won't you help to sing ♪
♪ These songs of freedom? ♪
♪ 'Cause all I ever have ♪
♪ Redemption songs ♪
♪ (Guitar break) ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Emancipate yourselves
from mental slavery ♪
♪ None but ourselves
can free our mind ♪
♪ Wo! ♪
♪ Have no fear for
atomic energy ♪
♪ 'Cause none of them-a
can-a stop-a the time ♪
♪ How long shall they
kill our prophets ♪
♪ While we stand
aside and look? ♪
♪ Yes, some say it's
just a part of it ♪
♪ We've got to
fulfill the book ♪
♪ Won't you help to sing ♪
♪ These songs of freedom? ♪
♪ 'Cause all I ever had ♪
♪ Redemption songs ♪
♪ All I ever had ♪
♪ These songs of freedom ♪
♪ Songs of freedom ♪
♪ ♪